const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '503 − 307 =', answer: '196', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '607 − 209 =', answer: '398', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '902 − 205 =', answer: '697', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '705 − 107 =', answer: '598', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '804 − 206 =', answer: '598', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '902 − 507 =', answer: '395', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '804 − 608 =', answer: '196', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '706 − 504 =', answer: '202', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '803 − 506 =', answer: '297', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '607 − 403 =', answer: '204', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];